男人:你好.
Man: Hello.
迈克:晚上好,
Mike: Good evening sir, wouldn't you and the Mrs.
先生,
like to put the thrill back into your marriage by touring Europe for just
难道你不愿意和您太太每天花费很少的钱去欧洲旅游来向你们的婚姻注入激情吗?
pennies a day?
本:没有特点.
Ben:Not particularly.
迈克:本.
Mike: Ben!
本,你知道的,迈克,爸爸告诉过你,他不会买任何你销售的东西.
Ben: You know Mike, dad told you he wouldn't buy anything you're selling.
迈克:知道,
Mike: Yeah, well listen twerp...young man.
听着蠢货……年轻人.让我告诉你那个发发疯旅游吧.
Let me tell you about Va Va Voom tours.
你介意我叫你年轻人吗?
Would you mind if I called you young man?
本:我喜欢.
Ben: I would prefer it.
迈克:那好,我告诉你,我喜欢……啊,也许我应该和这屋子的主人谈谈.
Mike: Well I'll tell you what I'd prefer....Ah, perhaps I should speak to the man of the house.
本:你等着,妈妈!
Ben: You got it.Mum!
麦琪:本,别嚷嚷.
Maggie: Ben, don't yell.
本:电话,一个恶心的推销员.
Ben: Telephone, some skuzzy sales guy.
麦琪:你好,迈克.
Maggie: hello Mike.
迈克:你好,西维尔太太,我有方法将激情再次注入你的婚姻.他们让我这么说的,妈妈.这只是一次巧合.
Mike: Hello Mrs.Seaver, I've got the way to put the sizzle back in your
marriage.They make me say this mum.It's just a coincidence
麦琪:迈克,当你得到这份工作的时候,我们已经经历过了.
Maggie: Mike, we went through this when you got this job.
迈克:还有,我想让你知道,
Mike: well I'll have you know mam,
我们的包办旅游去浪漫的地方,比如巴黎,罗马
that our package tours to romantic places like Paris, Rome,
和巴塞罗那,从来没有这么便宜过.
and Barcelona, have never been cheaper.
麦琪:你爸爸也不会同意.
Maggie: Neither has your father.
迈克:求你了,妈妈.只是一次花费很少的欧洲旅行.
Mike: please mum.Just one little all expense trip to Europe.
麦琪:迈克,哪天你爸爸同意去欧洲旅游,
Maggie: Mike, the day your dad springs for a trip to Europe is the day
猪就能飞.
pigs fly.
杰森,我还是不敢相信你已经同意了.
Jason, I still can't believe you did this.
杰森:我所要做的就是摘掉吝啬鬼的帽子.
Jason: what do I have to do to lose the underserved reputation for being
stingy?
埃迪:支付出租车的钱应该不会痛心.
Ed: Springing for a taxi wouldn't hurt.
杰森:行了,如果全家人去机场送我们,那样更好.
Jason: Com on.I just thought it would be nice if the whole family saw us off to the airport
奶奶:别听他的,杰森.
Grandma: Don't listen to him Jason.
当岳父母的就应该提供照顾孩子的服务.
Babysitting taxi services, that's what in-laws are for.
杰森:呵呵,这是他们负责.
Jason: Huhu.That's what they're for.
本:嗨,爸爸,
Ben: Hey dad, since we are at the airport,
机场到了,能让开萝尔在货物处下车吗?
can we drop Carol off at airfreight?
开萝尔:你知道,有些人拒绝带我去欧洲已经够坏了,
Carol: You know, it's bad enough that some people refuse to take me to
Europe, but do you have to squeeze me back here with Ben, the pesthole
本:能把开萝尔系在行李架上吗?
Ben: can we tie Carol to the luggage rack?
杰森:我不管;我去欧洲了.
Jason: I don't care; I'm going to Europe.
麦琪:开萝尔,这也是个浪漫的假日.
Maggie: Carol, this is a romantic holiday too.
我跟你爸爸单独庆祝我们的结婚纪念日的一丁点时间.
A little time for your dad and I to be alone and celebrate our anniversary.
杰森:而且忘记我们还有孩子.
Jason: And forget that we have kids.
埃迪:希望我可以忘记.
Ed: Wish I could forget.
奶奶:包括孩子,我们将度过丰富的一周.开萝尔,
Grandma: Besides kids, we are going to have a grand week together.
我终于有机会教你化妆了.还有本,
Carol, I finally get to teach you about make up.
刺绣不是没有男子气的.毕竟,现在是80年代了.
And Ben, it is not unmanly to embroider.After all, it is the eighties.
克莉丝:现在是90年代,外婆.
Chrissy: It is the nineties grandma.
埃迪:克莉丝,别把你奶奶弄糊涂了.
Ed: Christine, don't confuse your grandma.
迈克:外公,这,这,这.靠边.
Mike: Grandpa, here, here, here.Pull over.
麦琪:杰森,头等舱.我没想到.
Maggie: Jason, first class!I had no idea.
迈克:我也没想到.
Mike: Neither did I.
迈克:不,不.你们的还没有到.是我的.
Mike: No, no.It's not your stop.It's mine.
杰森:你的!
Jason: Your!
迈克:是呀.因为我卖了这么多票,
Mike: Yeah.See I sold so many trips that I got one of our collegiate tours
我得到一次免费旅游.
for free.
开萝尔:迈克也去欧洲?
Carol: Mikes going to Europe too!
麦琪:你怎么没提到?
Maggie: Why didn't you mention it?
杰森:是呀.本来还想这是一次我和你妈妈的浪漫旅游.有你在……
Jason: Yeah.This is supposed to be a romantic tour for your mum and I.With you around...
迈克:放松.我们决不会同时出现在一个城市里.我不会在你们附近的.我在幸福旅途中.
Mike: Relax.We won't be in any of the same cities at the same time.I won't be anywhere near you guys.I'm on a good tour.
杰森:好了啦.36D.
Jason: There it is.36D.
麦琪:哦,不.我的是36F.
Maggie: Oh no.I have 36F.
杰森:哦,对不起,能跟我换个位置吗?
Jason: Oh.Excuse me, would you switch with me please?
男人:不行.
Man: no.
杰森:你瞧,我妻子和我参加那些浪漫城市旅游,
Jason: well you see,
和……
my wife and I are on one of those romantic cities tours and...
男人:我也是.你还没听抱怨呢.
Man: Well so am I.You don't hear me carping.
我妻子的座位在厕所边上.
My wife's way back there with the bathroom.
杰森:你们为什么不坐在一起呢?
Jason: Why don't you sit together?
男人:为了孩子们的缘故.只是为了安全,我们从不同时出行.
Man: For the kids sake.Just for security, we never travel together.
马基:好了,杰森,亲爱的.坐下吧.打扰了.
Maggie: It's ok Jason honey.Just sit.Excuse me.
机长:我是诺亚机长.
Captain: This is captain Noah.
今天我们的起飞会有些推迟.请回到候机室,
There will be a slight delay in out departure today.
等我们把动物两个两个地装上飞机.
Kindly return to the terminal, where we load the animals two by two.
杰森:花生.
Jason: There go the peanuts.
(同时,在另外一个航班上,在头等舱)
(Meanwhile, on another flight, in first class)
迈克:不管怎么说,女士们,
Mike: Anyway ladies, I was just as stunned as you were when they put me
我和你们一样吃惊,当他们把我放在女生联谊会团里.我想发发疯旅游公司一定知道他们为什么这样做.
on this Sorority tour.I guess Va Va Voom tours knows what they are doing.
女孩:你遗漏了一个发,应该是发发发疯旅游公司.
Girl: You forgot a Va, it's Va Va Va Voom tours.
迈克:我怎么会忘?我为这个公司打工.
Mike: How could I forget?And I work for the company.
女孩2:你以前去过欧洲吗?
Girl 2: Have you been to Europe before?
迈克:哎,我对欧洲了如指掌.
Mike: Ok, I know that place like the back of my hand.
小妞,你们刚去过列支敦士登.
Deb, you juts marched through Liechtenstein.
女孩3:打扰一下.你刚才是说你在发发发疯旅游公司工作?
Girl 3: Excuse me.Did you just say that you work for Va Va Va Voom tours?
迈克:对,对,对,是的.
Mike: Yeah yeah yeah yes.
女孩3:你有没有发现,根据线路,
Girl 3: Do you realize, according to the itinerary,
我们不会去凭吊梵高的墓地.
we're not visiting the grave of Van Gogh?
迈克:身体健康.
Mike: Guzenteit.
女孩3:认真地,我是说,我不是来欧洲玩的.你呢?
Girl 3: Seriously, I mean, I didn't come to Europe to party.Did you?
女孩:玩!玩!
Girls: Party!Party!
女孩:没关系.
Girl 3: never mind.
迈克:等等,等等,等会儿.你确定你是与女生联谊会一起的?
Mike: Wait, wait wait a minute.Are you sure you're here with the sorority tour?
女孩3:这是女生联谊会团?
Girl 3: This is a sorority tour?
女孩:是的,宝贝.
Girl: Yeah babe.
迈克:行了.我们没有理由不成为好姐妹.
Mike: Come on.There is no reason we cannot get along like sisters.
笑一笑,闹一闹.
A little laughing, horseplay,
枕头大战
pillow fights.
女孩3:我去没有嘻嘻哈哈的舱位.
Girl 3: I'll be in the non-giggling section.
女孩:唉,迈克,
Girl 2: Ah Mike, I know what I wanted to ask.
我知道我想问什么.
When we get to France,
当我们到了法国,你能告诉我一美圆能兑换多少法郎吗?
can you tell me how many francs you can get for a dollar?
迈克:吃不准.如果他们都是奶牛,一个.
Mike: That depends.If they're all beef, one.
机长:我是诺亚机长.对不起,延迟了三小时.请大家就座.
Captain: This is Captain Noah again.Sorry about the three hour delay.Please take your seats.
杰森:你怎么想的,他们把大象运到欧洲?
Jason: Well how did you think they got elephants to Europe?
对不起,我爱我的妻子.
Sorry, I love my wife.
男人:对不起,我也爱我老婆.
Man: Sorry I love my wife too.
麦琪:杰森,放松点.
Maggie: Jason, just relax.
明天我们就可以在巴黎庆祝我们的结婚纪念日了.
Tomorrow we are going to be celebrating our anniversary in Paris.
杰森:是呀.瞧瞧我怎么作为一个大男孩.
Jason: Yes.See how I aced the big guy.
麦琪:杰森,浪漫呀.
Maggie: Jason, romance.
杰森:哦,是呀.
Jason: Oh yes.
麦琪:杰森,亲爱的,我想回到亨利饭店.
Maggie: Jason honey, I want to go back to Henris.
杰森:哦,是呀.我也是.我们去哪里才能找到那么物美价廉的饭菜呢?
Jason: Oh yes.So do I.Where else can you get such great food at sensible prices?
麦琪:那儿也是你向我求婚的地方.
Maggie: It's also where you proposed to me.
杰森:这是我首要原因.
Jason: That was my A reason.
机长:请注意,乘客们.
Captain: Attention passengers.Prepare for arrival in historic Barcelona city,
准备降落在历史上着名的巴塞罗那,那儿我相信你会陶醉于美景中的.
where I'm sure you'll enjoy the scenery.
迈克:好了,好了,下一辆巴士一定是我们的了.我确定.
Mike: Alright, alright, the next bus will be ours.I'm sure of it.
女孩2:你已经这样说了一个小时了.
Girl 2: You have been saying that for the last hour.
女孩们:就是!
Girls: Yeah!
女孩:那么我们的行李在哪?
Girl: And where's our luggage?
女孩们:是呀!
Girls: Yeah!
迈克:行了,妹妹们.
Mike: Come on sisters.Don't turn on me now.
别枪口对准我.尤其在你们已经告诉我所谓的秘密友谊之后.
Especially after you've shown me the secret handshake.
女孩1:我来这是为了见识欧洲的.
Girl 1: I came here to see Europe.
而不是站在这个陌生城市的中心.
Not stand here in the middle of some foreign city.
迈克:嗨,行了.你没有看文明小姐抱怨吧,是吗?
Mike: Hey come on.You don't see Miss Culture here complaining, do you?
女孩3:实际上,我很喜欢观察西班牙的真实生活,到处走动看看.(她讲西班牙语;意思是说在街道和咖啡馆才能找到真正的西班牙.)
Girl 3: Actually, I was enjoying watching this impromptu view of Spanish life, moving hither and yon before us.(She speaks Spanish; the meaning is The heart of Spain can be found in the streets and cafes)
女孩1:我乘出租汽车.
Girl 1: I'm taking a cab.
女孩2:我也是.
Girl 2: Me too.
迈克:等一会儿;坐出租汽车会花很多钱的.
Mike: Wait a minute; cabs cost a lot of money.
女孩们:我们富有.
Girls: We're rich.
女孩3:男孩子,有些人怎么这么肤浅呀.
Girl 3: Boy, some people can be so shallow.
迈克:是啊.嗨,你们不介意搭我一程吧,是吧?
Mike: Yeah.Hey, you wouldn't mind giving me a ride, would you?
迈克:嗨,他们去哪儿啊,一张车票要四十美元?
Mike: Hey where do they get off charging forty dollars for a bus ticket?
女孩3:不是四十美圆,是四美圆.
Girl 3: Not forty dollars, four dollars.
迈克:嗨,嗨.西班牙钱还不错.
Mike: Hey hey.This Spanish money is ok.
女孩3:我看我的书.
Girl 3: I'll read my book.
迈克:欧洲裸体.
Mike: Nude in Europe.
女孩:这就是一本艺术书.没有什么好感到羞愧的.
Girl 3: It's just an art book.And nothing to be ashamed of.Put it away.
放下.放下.放下.
Put it away.Put it away.
迈克:你能放松点吗?这里面没有什么值得看的.
Mike: Would you relax.There's nothing worth looking at in there.
全部是石头.
They're all stone
女孩3:是的,你不懂,艺术家的手可以拿起冰冷的石头,并且能把它变成崇高境界的性爱作品.
Girl 3: yeah but understand, the hands of an artist can take cold stone and turn
it into a sublime level of eroticism
迈克:那是在哪一页?
Mike: What page is that on?
女孩3:你为什么来欧洲?
Girl 3: Why did you come to Europe?
迈克:即使我选择了一个地方,
Mike: Well I figured a place with sixty eight million women who couldn't
那儿6800万女人对我说的话一点不懂,也不是完全糟透了.
understand a word I said couldn't be all bad.
你怎么会最终在女生联谊会的团?
How did you end up on a sorority tour?
女孩3:我被一个不诚实的电话推销员误导了.
Girl 3: I was misled by some sleazy phone salesman.
迈克:他没有提及他的名字,提了吗?
Mike: he didn't happen to mention his name did he?
女孩3:没有,为什么?
Girl 3: No, why?
迈克:没有什么原因.
Mike: No reason.
女孩:我但愿能很快到达宾馆.
Girl 3: I hope we get to the hotel soon.
我想在关门之前参观一些博物馆.
I want to see some of the museums before closing time.
迈克:好呀,但是那些塑像什么地方都不会去.有没有人告诉过你,你有很强的幽默感.
Mike: Alright, but the statues aren't going any place.Did anyone ever tell you that
you have got a great sense of humor
女孩3:没有呀.
Girl3: No.
迈克:将来也不会有人告诉你的.嗨,瞧,
Mike: No one ever will.Hey look, I didn't mean to say anything to upset you.
我并不是想说一些你恼火的事情.希望这些裸体能给你好运.我希望你的假期没有完全浪费.
And good luck with the nude thing.I hope your vacation isn't a total waste.
女孩3:谢谢.还有请,如果有人问你,就说你是加拿大人.
Girl 3: thank you.And please, if anyone asks you, say you're Canadian.
迈克:下午好,先生.您好,先生(西班牙语).你好,先生.您好,先生(西班牙语).他们这里有什么招待客人的?你是第一个触摸我灵魂的女人.你是第一个触摸我灵魂的女人(西班牙语).
Mike: Good afternoon sir.Buenos Dias senore.Hello sir, holo senore.What have they got
in here for sinorita?You are the first woman ever to touch my soul.Tu
es la primera muhere que mihad metado me elmare.You!Wait a minute
迈克和女孩3:你不是住这宾馆吧?
Mike and Girl 3: You're not staying at this hotel?
迈克:不,那太糟了.
Mike: Well not that that's bad.
女孩3:不.我是说这可不像牙疼.
Girl 3: No.I mean it's not like a toothache.
迈克:(你说的简单)
Mike: (easy fro you to say)
接待:下午好,先生.
Reception: Buenos dias inbenidos.
迈克:你好.
Mike: Holow.
女孩3:这是示意.(说西班牙语.意思是:先生,我们是发发发疯旅游团.)
Girl 3: It's ola.(Speaks Spanish.The meaning is: Sir, we are with the Va Va Va Voom tour)
接待:发发疯.
Reception: Va Va Voom.
迈克:不,你漏了一个发.
Mike: No, you left pout one Va.
女孩3:(西班牙语,意思是说:先生,我们有住宿凭证.)
Girl 3: (Spanish, meaning: Sir, we have our hotel vouchers)
接待:(西班牙语,意思是:那些发发发疯猪欠我两百西班牙银币.
Reception: (Spanish meaning: Those Va Va Va Voom swine owe me two hundred pesetas.
你们的住宿凭证没有用,除非你们把它当作卫生纸.)
Your vouchers are useless unless you are in need of toilet paper)
迈克:啊,告诉他我在这个公司工作.
Mike: Ah, tell him that I work for the company.
接待:(西班牙语:如果我能抓到那些畜生,我一定狠狠教训他们.)
Reception: (Spanish: If I ever catch up with those beasts, I will severely reprimand them)
迈克:告诉他我经营这家公司.
Mike: Tell him I run the company.
女孩3:迈克,你……(西班牙语:这位是发发发疯公司的总裁.)
Girl 3: Mike, you...(In Spanish: This man is President of Va Va Va Voom)
迈克:嗨,这是我最后一次在这个镇里对人说你好了.
Mike: hey man, this is the last time I say hallow to anybody in this town.
麦琪:小甜心.巴黎到了!
Maggie: Sweetheart.Paris!
杰森:如果你不介意的话,让一下.
Jason: If you don't mind, excuse me.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,真漂亮.瞧!
Maggie: Oh honey, it's so pretty.Look!
麦琪:杰森,笑一笑,我们到了.
Maggie: Jason smile, we're here.
杰森:是呀,迟了四个小时.我们的免费巴士怎么回事?
Jason: Yeah, four hours late.Whatever happened to our free your bus?
麦琪:我告诉你一个事实,小甜心,
Maggie: Well to tell you the truth sweetheart,
我喜欢单独和你在一起.
I kind of enjoy being alone with you.
杰森:是呀,我也是.法语中的收据是什么单词?
Jason: Yeah, me too.What's the French word for receipt?
麦琪:杰森,只是出租车的车程.
Maggie: Jason, it's only a cab ride.
杰森:也是,
Jason: yeah, but who knows what round about route this criminal's taking
但是谁知道这个罪恶的家伙是不是带我们绕路?
us on.
出租车司机:法语里面的收据单词跟英语里面的一样.
Cab driver: the French word for receipt is receipt.
杰森:啊.哦!
Jason: Ah.Oh!
麦琪:亲爱的,休息一下,享受旅途吧.
Maggie: Honey, just sit back and enjoy the ride.
杰森:我会坐好的.我不能保证我能旅途愉快.
Jason: I'll sit back.I can't promise I'll enjoy myself.
麦琪:哦,瞧,艾非尔铁塔.
Maggie: Oh look, the Eiffel Tower!
杰森:大烂东西.
Jason: Big stinking deal.
麦琪:里斯本大街,那么我们的旅馆应该就在那.
Maggie: The Rue de l'esperant, that means our hotel should be right there.
亲爱的,我们不能住这.我们怎么办?
Honey, we can't stay here.What do we do?
杰森:我不知道.
Jason: I don't know.
出租车司机:先生,夫人,
Cab Driver: Monsieur, Madame, perhaps while you are discussing this,
或许当你们讨论这些的时候,我可以跟老熟人打个招呼.
I will renew an old acquaintance.
女孩3:你好.这是电话?
Girl 3: Ola.Esta telephone aqui?
男人:是.
Man: Si.
女孩:谢谢.
Girl 3: Gracias.
迈克:回去!
Mike: Pst!
女孩3:啊!
Girl 3: Ah!
迈克:听着,听着.
Mike: Look, look.I don't think it's safe for me to be out in the open
我觉得我在像这样的野外很不安全.这镇上有人会杀了我.
like this.Somebody in this town wants to kill me.
女孩:对,是我.
Girl 3: Yeah, me.
迈克:你什么意思?
Mike: What do you mean?
女孩:迈克,我们所在的旅游团.
Girl 3: Mike, the tour we're on.The tour you run.It's gone bust.
你开的旅游公司.旅游泡汤了.我们没有交通工具,
We have no transportation,
没有住处,没有吃的.
no hotel, no meals.
迈克:因此这不可能影响到我们的海滩时刻.
Mike: So this is no way affects our beach time.
女孩3:再见.
Girl 3: Goodbye.
迈克:喂,喂,你去哪里?
Mike: Whe, whe, where are you going?
女孩3:找个电话.
Girl 3: To find a phone.
我想知道是否至少我们的返程机票没有问题.
I want to see if at least our return air tickets are good.
迈克:告诉你,我也打算去做同样的事情.
Mike: You know, I was just about to do the same thing.
女孩3:是,是.谢谢你的答复.谢谢.
Girl 3: Si, si.Muchos gracias por su et ida.Gracias.
迈克:怎么样,他们怎么说?我们的机票有效吗?
Mike: well, what did they say?Are our tickets good?
女孩3:当然,他们仍然有效,巴塞罗那任何一家旅行社能把这些机票换成今天的航班.
Girl 3: Yeah, they are still good, and any travel agent in Barcelona will exchange them
for a flight out today
迈克:好呀!
Mike: Yeah!
女孩:需要1400美金.
Girl 3: For fourteen hundred dollars!
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
女孩:一个人.经济舱.头等舱需要1800美金.
Girl 3: Each.For coach.Eighteen hundred dollars first class.
迈克:哇.习惯了坐头等舱,
Mike: Wow.It's going to be so tough flying coach after getting used to
坐经济舱太痛苦了.行了.只是个玩笑.
first class.Come on.It was only a joke.
艾米:你不明白吗,迈克?
Amy: Don't you get it Mike?We are stranded in Europe.
我们是被陷在欧洲了.我们有两张回程票,只有在巴黎有效,
We have a pair of tickets that are good only in Paris, in six days.
有效期六天.一个离我们500英里的城市.
A city five hundred miles away.
迈克:事实上,我相信这里你需要使用千米.
Mike: Actually, I believe here you use kilometers.
艾米:对于一个连法郎和热狗的区别都不知道的家伙,
Amy: What was I expecting from a guy who doesn't know the difference between
我们能指望什么?
Francs and hot dogs?
迈克:我确定我知道.法郎是在端部有小节的东西.
Mike: I sure do.Francs are ones with the little knots on the ends.
顺便说句,你不要吃法郎.
By the way, you shouldn't eat those.Fine, you weren't the only victim here.
好了,你又不是唯一的受害者.我意思是说,
I mean this trip was supposed to be my reward for selling more tickets
因为我卖出的票比别人多,这趟旅行是对我的奖励.
than anybody else.I mean,
我说,我甚至为我父母订了巴黎最烂的饭店.
I even booked my parents into the worst hotel in Paris.
艾米:你为了卖旅游票,你误导了你自己的父母.
Amy: You misled your own parents, just to sell a tour?
迈克:误导.嗨,
Mike: Misled.Hey, my parents wanted a little romance in their tour.
我父母希望他们的旅行有些浪漫色彩.我确信他们会得到的.
I'm sure they'll find some.
艾米:而且我想,你对那个爱好文化的女孩也同样的误导了.
Amy: And I suppose you did the same for a girl interested in culture.
迈克:哦,是呀.
Mike: Oh sure.There was this one girl,
有这么一个姑娘,她只想去看墓地和博物馆.我是说,
she only wanted to see graves and museums.
如果一个东西有脉搏,她就不感兴趣.
I mean if it had a pulse, she wasn't interested,
艾米:她的名字是艾米 柏德莉亚?
Amy: Was her name Amy Boudelier?
迈克:是呀.嗨,你怎么了.哦.
Mike: Yeah.Hey how did you.Oh.
艾米:我恨你.我恨你.
Amy: I hate you.I hate you.
迈克:我们是美国人.让我们树立个榜样.
Mike: we are Americans.Let set an example.
艾米:你让我恶心.
Amy: You make me sick.
迈克:嗨,瞧.
Mike: hey look.
艾米:我把我的每一分钱都花在这次虚假的旅游上了,因为你.而且我不是那种打个电话就能向老爸求救的女孩子.
Amy: I spent every penny I had on this sham of a tour, because of you.And I am not the kind of girl who can just go call daddy to help me out.
迈克:保留那种想法.
Mike: Hold that thought.
开萝尔:我去取报纸.
Carol: I'm going to go get the paper.
本:哦,不要让你的周末太早达到高潮,开萝尔.
Ben: Oh, don't let your weekend peak too early Carol.
本:本,奶奶和爷爷去哪里了?
Carol: Ben, where's grandma and grandpa?
本,在楼上,给克莉丝洗澡.
Ben: Upstairs giving Chrissy a bath.
埃迪:回到这,你这个小……
Ed: Come back here you little...
克莉丝:不!
Chrissy: No!
埃迪:克莉丝!
Ed: Christine!
奶奶:本,当水热了,
Grandma: Bennie, while the waters warm, you want to hop in the tub?
你想跳进浴缸吗?我给你洗后背.
I'll do your back.
本:好的.
Ben: Ok.
奶奶:哦,还有开萝尔,在我洗完本的后背之后,你和我去收拾你的梳妆抽屉,把垃圾扔掉.
Grandma: Oh, and Carol, as soon as I finish with Bens back, you and I
are going to go through your make up drawer and throw out the trash
开萝尔:好呀.
Carol: Swell
(电话响)
(Phone rings)
开萝尔:喂.喂.你能大声一点吗?对,我会说些西班牙语.(是的,我们付电话费.)
Carol: Hello.Hello.Could you speak up please?Si, hablo un poco d'espanol.(Yes we'll pay for calls)
迈克:听着,叫我妹妹开萝尔.她是个像你一样的语言天才.
Mike: Look, ask for my sister Carol.She's a language geek like you.
艾米:我想跟开萝尔讲话.
Amy: Me gusteria hablo con Carol.
开萝尔:我是开萝尔.
Carol: Estes Carol.
艾米:开萝尔.
Amy: Carol.
迈克:很好,告诉她我需要一些钱,因此我需要妈妈和爸爸的宾馆号码……等一下,开萝尔说英语的,我也会.嗨,开萝尔!
Mike: Ok, tell her I need some money, so I need the number of mum
and dads hotel...wait a minute, Carol speaks English, so do it.Hey Carol
开萝尔:是.欧洲怎么样,迈克?我没去那里,你知道.
Carol: ola.So how's Europe Mike?I'm not there you know.
迈克:开萝尔,听着,因此我需要妈妈和爸爸在巴黎的宾馆号码.性了,
Mike: Carol, look, I need the number of mum and dads hotel in Paris.
这是紧急事件.我现在束手无策,那个旅游公司破产了.
Alright, it's an emergency.I'm stranded and the tour company's gone bust.
开萝尔:别挂,迈克,有另外的电话.
Carol: Hold on Mike, I've got another call.
迈克:不,开萝尔不要.
Mike: No Carol don't.
开萝尔:喂.
Carol: Hello.
杰森:开萝尔,电话费不便宜,
Jason: Carol, this isn't cheap so I'm going to make this quick.
我们只好说的快一点儿.我们在巴黎没有住线路上的宾馆.
We will not be staying in the hotel in Paris that's on our itinerary.
开萝尔:那么欧洲怎么样,我没去那里,你知道.
Carol: So how' Europe, I'm not there you know.
杰森:开萝尔!
Jason: Carol!
开萝尔:请,哦,请告诉我你们在享受的愉快经历.
Carol: please o please tell me what a wonderful time you're having.
麦琪:你们怎么样?
Maggie: How's everybody?
杰森:你们怎么样?
Jason: How's everybody?
开萝尔:这样,
Carol: Well,
埃迪:克莉丝,穿上鞋子.
Ed: Chrissy, put these shoes on.
开萝尔: 克莉丝赤身裸体地在屋子里面跑,还有,
Carol: Chrissy's running through the house naked screaming and uh,
哦,本和外婆在洗澡.
bens taking a bath with grandma.
杰森:一切都好.听着,这丰富的旅行出了点事情.
Jason: Everything's fine.Listen something has happened on this crummy tour.
开萝尔:我听说了.
Carol: I heard.
杰森:从谁那里得知的?
Jason: From who?
开萝尔:迈克.我让他在另外一通电话上等着呢.
Carol: Mike.I have him on the other line.
杰森:哦,好的.这样,
Jason: Oh yeah.Well the next time he sells anything, you tell him.
如果下次他推销什么的话,你告诉他.等一下,他打电话要钱吗?
Wait a minute, is he calling collect?
哦,他正站在那里保持接通,花我的钱呀?
Oh he's standing there on hold right now soaking up my money?
开萝尔:毫无疑问,玩的开心.
Carol: And no doubt enjoying it.
杰森:哦,那么现在你告诉他……我这次赢不了了.
Jason: Oh well now what you tell him is...I can't win this one.
麦琪:就给她宾馆的电话,走.
Maggie: just give her the number of the hotel and let's go.
杰森:听着,宾馆的电话是……
Jason: Listen, the number of the hotel is...
克莉丝:哈哈哈.
Chrissy: ha ha ha.
杰森:零,宾馆的名字叫……
Jason: Zero, and the name of the hotel is the...
麦琪:乔治 六
Maggie: George six.
杰森:乔治 六.那是全巴黎最昂贵的宾馆.哦.
Jason: The George six.It's the most expensive hotel in the whole of Paris.Oh.
开萝尔:喂,爸爸,你还在吗?喂.
Carol: Hello, dad, you still there?Hello.
迈克:开萝尔.
Mike: Carol.
开萝尔:迈克,你还在线吗?
Carol: Mike, are you still there.
迈克:是,保持通话花费的是爸爸的钱.
Mike: Yep, just standing here soaking up dad's money.
跟你说实话,我就喜欢这样.
To tell you the truth, I kind of enjoy it.
行了,那么为什么你打电话给我?
Right, so why did you call me?
麦琪:杰森,我记得二十年前,
Maggie: Jason, I remember twenty years ago when it was a thrill just to
哪怕就是进这个宾馆的洗手间都让人激动不已.
go to the bathroom in this hotel.
杰森:现在还是.呵呵.发发发疯.
Jason: it still is.Ho ho.Va Va Va Voom.
麦琪:楼下商场买的.
Maggie: From the shop downstairs.
杰森:哇!
Jason: Wow!
麦琪:只有1500法郎.怎么样?
Maggie: Only fifteen hundred francs.What do you think?
杰森:亲爱的,很漂亮.
Jason: Honey, it's gorgeous.
麦琪:对于这个价格,你不退缩吗?
Maggie: You didn't wince at the price.
杰森:是的,那是因为我不知道今天的汇率,
Jason: Yeah, well that's because I don't know the exchange rate today
现在我还不想知道.
and I'd like to keep it that way for a while.
麦琪:亲爱的,你变的如此可爱,对于我们花费的所有钱.
Maggie: Honey, you're being so sweet about all the money we're spending.
杰森:其实重要的是我们在一起.而且我们在巴黎,
Jason: Well the important thing is that we are together.
这是我们的结婚纪念日.那么,结婚纪念日快乐.
And we're in Paris, and it's our anniversary.So, happy anniversary.
麦琪:结婚纪念日快乐.
Maggie: Happy anniversary.
杰森:当你在下面买东西时候,我给你买了样东西,
Jason: When you were down buying that,
我想让你瞧瞧.
I bought you something that I'd kind of like to see on you.
麦琪:杰森!哦!喔!
Maggie: Jason!Oh!Urghhh!
杰森:提醒我给开门的小费.
Jason: Remind me to tip that doorman.
迈克:铃响了,
Mike: It's ringing, it's ringing.
铃响了.如果我妈发现她可怜的儿子有困难,
When my mum finds out that her little boy is in trouble,
我可以感觉到她有多着急.
heck I can just here her now.
麦琪:杰森.
Maggie: Jason,
杰森:是,是,是,小甜心.是阑尾炎,我们正送你去医院.
Jason: Yes, yes, yes sweetheart.It's appendicitis but we're taking you to the hospital
一切都会好的.
Everything's going to be fine.
麦琪:哦,小甜心,你要知道,这衣服其实是3000法郎,也就是600美元.
Maggie: Oh sweetheart, you should know the dress really cost three thousand francs and that's six hundred dollars.
杰森:哦!
Jason: Ewwww!
(电话响)
(Phone ringing)
迈克:妈妈,我和一个疯女孩被困在西班牙了.我说的是实话.是真的.
Mike: Mum, I'm stranded in Spain with a crazy woman.I'm practicing.Not that it isn't true.
迈克:嗨,你知道你至少可以做你那部分的事情.
Mike: Hey, you know the least you could do is do your part.
艾米:我不喜欢这样.
Amy: I don't like this.
迈克:好了,只是看起来不舒服.很完美了.
Mike: ok, just look uncomfortable.That's perfect.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的, 我毁掉了我们的浪漫之旅.
杰森:哦,你没有毁掉任何东西.我们在一起,而且我们在巴黎.嘿,瞧!
00:23:00,700
Maggie: Oh honey, I've ruined our romantic trip. Jason: Oh, you haven't ruined anything.We're together and we are in Paris.Hey voila!